Sabrina Prefer

(561) 706-8534

Philadelphia, PA

seprefer@gmail.com

Profile

Experienced Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the operations industry. Skilled in Operations Management, Team Building, Public Speaking, and Time Management. Strong operations professional with a Master of Business Administration (MBA) focused in International Business from Florida Atlantic University and a Six Sigma Black Belt.

Work Experience

Area Manager

Amazon, Middletown, DE

February 2017-Present

- Manage 150+ associates at a 1.2 million square foot facility in addition to daily duties which include but are not limited to: delivering performance feedback and coaching to drive results, creating process improvement, balancing headcount flow within the department and leading engagement initiatives
- Maintained lowest injury rate of any other area manager with a comparable headcount year to date by leading safety initiatives, audits and helping to lead the Associate Safety Committee
- Led a project to improve stow productivity for stowing shoes and apparel by reconfiguring bin space. After the first test launch, productivity was seen to increase by about 15%
- Created diversity initiatives such as founding and being president of Women @ Amazon Delaware chapter
- Main point of contact for all radio management activity within the building and compliance of radio return

Area Manager

Amazon, West Deptford, NJ

- Selected to launch a new, nearby fulfillment center. As an area manager in this type of facility, duties expanded from being in charge of overseeing one shift to being in charge of the entire night shift operation
- · Prepared for and launched the building as well as trained all staff on the ins and outs of the operation
- In addition to being in charge of all operations, also oversees any and all safety, HR, IT, and maintenance escalations as the building does not have these support teams. On site and on call for all night operations

Operations Manager

LA Fitness, Fort Myers, FL

December 2014-December 2016

- Manage employees and plant at 30K + square foot facility
- Personnel duties include scheduling, hiring, training, and management of 20+ employees
- Facility duties include responsibility for \$5 million in equipment; maintaining a safe, clean, healthy and fun environment for employees and customers
- Supervise customer check-in and membership control for over 1,400 members daily
- Provide high level customer relations when problems with membership and/or training occurs
- Member Service Manager: Resolves escalated member issues for the corporate office. This includes escalations that occurred not only in my facility, but in facilities all over the country

Guest Service Associate

European Wax Center, Estero, FL

February 2013-December 2014

- Managed the reservation book Complete responsibility to make sure all the appointments were properly scheduled along with rebooks and cancelations
- Handled all money for the center and reconciled daily receipts
- · Open/close center, prepared daily routine for all employees, along with daily shut down of store
- Trained new employees in all operating procedures
- Sales Sold all of our products, along with special long-term commitment and loyalty packages

Education

Florida Gulf Coast University

August 2011-December 2014

• Bachelor of Arts in Psychology (Interdisciplinary Studies Minor) GPA – 3.65

Florida Atlantic University

August 2015-August 2017

MBA - Master's in Business Administration (International Business Concentration) GPA – 3.7

Six Sigma Global Institute

Completed March 2018

Six Sigma Black Belt Certified